{
	"wordup": [
        {
            "Question": "A Pretentious Loiterer In A Religious House",
            "Answer": "Abbey-lubber",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Inability To Make Decisions",
            "Answer": "Abulia",
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Wart That Hangs Down Like A String",
            "Answer": "Acrochordon",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Plastic Tip On The End Of A Shoelace",
            "Answer": "Aglet",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Wire Cage Holding The Cork In A Bottle Of Champagne",
            "Answer": "Agraffe",
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Feverish Desire To Rip One’s Clothes Off",
            "Answer": "Apodysophilia",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Something That Appears Out Of Thin Air",
            "Answer": "Apport",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Copious But Meaningless Writing Or Talk",
            "Answer": "Argle-bargle",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Complete Freedom From Stress And Anxiety",
            "Answer": "Ataraxia",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Little Loops For A Belt On A Pair Of Trousers Or A Raincoat",
            "Answer": "Beckets",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Coarsly Abusive Language",
            "Answer": "Billingsgate",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Something That Wants To Be Grand But Is Only Bland",
            "Answer": "Blandiose",
        },
        {
            "Question": "To Brag Or Speak Pompously",
            "Answer": "Bloviate",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Delusion That You Are An Ox Or A Cow",
            "Answer": "Boanthropy",
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Strap That Holds Pant Legs In Place",
            "Answer": "Bowyang",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Hole In A Cask Or Barrel Where Liquid Is Poured In Or Drained Out",
            "Answer": "Bunghole",
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Shocking Thing",
            "Answer": "Bysen",
        },
        {
            "Question": "An Intense Flurry Of Activity To Finish Something By A Deadline",
            "Answer": "Charette",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Someone That Loves Nooks And Crannies",
            "Answer": "Chasmophile",
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Small Cheese",
            "Answer": "Cheeseling",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Another Name For Woodlice",
            "Answer": "Cheeselips",
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Rhetorical Device Of Repeating Some Words You’ve Used In Reverse Order",
            "Answer": "Chiasmus",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Noise That Feet Make When Your Shoes Are Full Of Water",
            "Answer": "Chork",
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Group Hired To Applaud At A Performance",
            "Answer": "Claque",
        },
        {
            "Question": "An Obsessive Desire To Lie Down",
            "Answer": "Clinomania",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Science Of Leg-Pulling",
            "Answer": "Codology",
        },
        {
            "Question": "To Feel Ill Because Of Excessive Eating Or Drinking",
            "Answer": "Crapulous",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Of Or Relating To Twilight",
            "Answer": "Crepuscular",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Bed Fluff That’s Lodged In Your Belly Button",
            "Answer": "Culf",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Shock You Feel When You First Jump Into Cold Water",
            "Answer": "Curglaff",
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Low Rumbling Sound Produced By The Bowels",
            "Answer": "Curmuring",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Loose Skin On A Cow’s Neck",
            "Answer": "Dewlap",
        },
        {
            "Question": "To Make Wet And Dirty By Dragging On The Ground",
            "Answer": "Draggle",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Decaying Matter In A Forest",
            "Answer": "Duff",
        },
        {
            "Question": "To Lay A Bottle On Its Side Long Enough To Drain The Few Drops Remaining",
            "Answer": "Duffifie",
        },
        {
            "Question": "German Word For The False Sensation Of Movement Felt When Looking Out Of A Stopped Train, You See Another Train Depart",
            "Answer": "Eisenbahnscheinbewegung",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Final Individual In A Species",
            "Answer": "Endling",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Constantly Hungry",
            "Answer": "Famelicose",
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Dangling Piece Of Curly Hair",
            "Answer": "Feat",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Metal Part Of A Pencil",
            "Answer": "Ferrule",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Having The Color Of A Dead Or Faded Leaf",
            "Answer": "Feuillemorte",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Someone Who Is Very Free With Money, Is A Generous Spender",
            "Answer": "Flahoolick",
        },
        {
            "Question": "To Laugh In A Disrespectful Or Jeering Way",
            "Answer": "Fleer",
        },
        {
            "Question": "To Behave In A Cowardly Manner",
            "Answer": "Flink",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Feverishly Plucking At The Bed Linens",
            "Answer": "Flocculating",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Sucking Honey From Flowers",
            "Answer": "Florisugent",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Overwhelmed By Unreasonable And Disproportionate Scolding",
            "Answer": "Forflitten",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Weary With Being Tossed About",
            "Answer": "Forwallowed",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Pretending To Work",
            "Answer": "Fudgelling",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Tightrope Walking",
            "Answer": "Funambuling",
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Legal Term Describing Goods Or Money That Can Be Replaced By Equivalent Items",
            "Answer": "Fungible",
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Wandering Beggar",
            "Answer": "Gaberlunzie",
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Warning Cry Shouted Before Throwing Slops From An Upstairs Window",
            "Answer": "Gardyloo",
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Gaelic Word For Both A Beautiful Fairy And A Hag In The Shape Of A Goat.",
            "Answer": "Glaistig",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Substance That Collects In The Bottom Of Your Pockets",
            "Answer": "Gnurr",
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Person Who Believes Everything He Or She Hears",
            "Answer": "Gobemouche",
        },
        {
            "Question": "One Who Stares For A Long Time At Things Happening On A Canal",
            "Answer": "Gongoozler",
        },
        {
            "Question": "To Have A Paralyzing Or Mesmerizing Effect On Someone",
            "Answer": "Gorgonize",
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Surgical Sponge Accidentally Left Inside A Patient’s Body",
            "Answer": "Gossypiboma",
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Double Handful Of Water",
            "Answer": "Gowpen",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Word For A High-Spirited Person In The 14Th Century",
            "Answer": "Great-willy",
        },
        {
            "Question": "To Silently Watch People While They’re Eating, Hoping They’ll Ask You To Join Them",
            "Answer": "Groak",
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Musical Timing Of 1/64",
            "Answer": "Hemidemisemiquaver",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Fear Of Long Words",
            "Answer": "Hippopotomonstrosesquippedaliophobia",
        },
        {
            "Question": "To Disgust Even Yourself",
            "Answer": "Idiorepulsive",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Excessive Reference To Oneself In The Third Person",
            "Answer": "Illeism",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Australian Word Meaning ‘A Small-Time Confidence Trickster’",
            "Answer": "Illywhacker",
        },
        {
            "Question": "This Word Is Used To Yell At Your Suboordinates When They’re Not Being Productive Enough",
            "Answer": "Imshi",
        },
        {
            "Question": "To Hide In The Bathroom",
            "Answer": "Incloacate",
        },
        {
            "Question": "To Apply Ointment To Someone Or Something",
            "Answer": "Inunct",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Breakfasty, Breakfastish, Of Or Relating To Breakfast",
            "Answer": "Jentacular",
        },
        {
            "Question": "To Fidget Or Shuffle",
            "Answer": "Jiffle",
        },
        {
            "Question": "To Pour With An Unsteady Hand",
            "Answer": "Jirble",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Death Caused By Overwork Or Job-Related Exhaustion",
            "Answer": "Karoshi",
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Scottish Word Meaning ‘Consipicuous, Easily Recognizable’",
            "Answer": "Kenspeckle",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Graffiti Found In Restrooms",
            "Answer": "Latrinalia",
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Fawning Person Who Is Eager To Obey Those In Power",
            "Answer": "Lickspittle",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Tail Of A Graduate’s Hood",
            "Answer": "Liripoop",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The White, Crescent Shaped Part At The Base Of A Nail",
            "Answer": "Lunule",
        },
        {
            "Question": "An Old Hag",
            "Answer": "Mackabroin",
        },
        {
            "Question": "To Blur In Printing",
            "Answer": "Mackle",
        },
        {
            "Question": "To Treat Someone Very Indulgently Or Protectively",
            "Answer": "Mollycoddle",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Strip Of Wood Or Metal That Separates Panes Of Glass In A Window",
            "Answer": "Muntin",
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Word Meaning Muttering, Murmuring.",
            "Answer": "Mussitation",
        },
        {
            "Question": "An Adjective That Means ‘More Than Usually Susceptible To The Cold’",
            "Answer": "Nesh",
        },
        {
            "Question": "To Build A Nest",
            "Answer": "Nidify",
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Person Who Deals With Things Of No Importance",
            "Answer": "Nihilarian",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Pleasurable Anticipation Of Success Before Any Actual Work Has Been Done",
            "Answer": "Nikhedonia",
        },
        {
            "Question": "An Effeminate Fellow, Especially Well-Dressed And Popular With Women",
            "Answer": "Nimfadoro",
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Lover Of Wine",
            "Answer": "Oenophile",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Fear Of Belly Buttons",
            "Answer": "Omphalophobia",
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Person Who Illegally Exports Sheep",
            "Answer": "Owler",
        },
        {
            "Question": "An Old Document In Which The Original Writing Has Been Scraped Off So That New Words Can Be Written Over It",
            "Answer": "Palimpsest",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Characterized By Extreme Optimism, Especially In The Face Of Adversity",
            "Answer": "Panglossian",
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Tax On Keeping Pigs In Royal Forests That Was Paid In Pigs",
            "Answer": "Pannage",
        },
        {
            "Question": "To Hold A Meeting While Walking",
            "Answer": "Pedeconference",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Other Side To A Hammer’s Striking Side",
            "Answer": "Peen",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Pleasant Smell That Accompanies Rain",
            "Answer": "Petrichor",
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Lawyer Whose Methods Are Underhanded Or Disreputable",
            "Answer": "Pettifogger",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Lights You See If You Close Your Eyes And Press Your Hands To Them",
            "Answer": "Phosphenes",
        },
        {
            "Question": "What You Call The Spots On Dice And Dominoes",
            "Answer": "Pips",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Offspring Of A Polar Bear And A Grizzly Bear",
            "Answer": "Pizzly Bear",
        },
        {
            "Question": "An Adjective Meaning ‘Liking To Wander’",
            "Answer": "Planeticose",
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Person Who Finds Joy And Comfort In Rainy Days",
            "Answer": "Pluviophile",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Fear Of Beards",
            "Answer": "Pogonophobia",
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Person Whose Job It Is To Taste Meats And Drinks Before Serving Them",
            "Answer": "Pregustator",
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Rare Word Meaning ‘Made With Gruel’",
            "Answer": "Pulmentarious",
        },
        {
            "Question": "An Adjective Meaning ‘Like Birds That Roll Themselves In Dust’ Or ‘Dust-Colored’",
            "Answer": "Pulveratricious",
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Stocky Person With A Rounded Body And Head, Thick Trunk, And A Tendency To Fat",
            "Answer": "Pyknic",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Season For Drinking",
            "Answer": "Quafftide",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Resembling A Marsh, Soggy And Soft",
            "Answer": "Quaggy",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The First Person You Meet After Leaving Your House On Some Special Occasion",
            "Answer": "Qualtagh",
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Small Shoot That Grows From The Root Of A Plant",
            "Answer": "Ratoon",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Foggy, Damp, And Cold",
            "Answer": "Rawky",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Seemingly Malevolent Bahavior Of Inanimate Objects",
            "Answer": "Resistentialism",
        },
        {
            "Question": "An Adjective Meaning Behind The Times Or Characteristic Of An Earlier Period",
            "Answer": "Retardataire",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Hairless And Moist Nose Of Some Animals",
            "Answer": "Rhinarium",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Medical Condition Otherwise Known As ‘A Runny Nose’",
            "Answer": "Rhinorrhea",
        },
        {
            "Question": "High-Waisted Skiing Pants With Shoulder Straps",
            "Answer": "Salopettes",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Unstressed, Flat Vowel Sound That Isn’t Represented By Any Of The Available Vowels",
            "Answer": "Schwa",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Collection Of Stock And Bond Certificates As Works Of Art",
            "Answer": "Scripophily",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Unfair Description Of Something Said Or Done To Make People Have A Bad Opinion Of Someone",
            "Answer": "Scurrilous",
        },
        {
            "Question": "An Adjective Meaning Unfamiliar, Rare, Strange, And Wonderful",
            "Answer": "Selcouth",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Tendency To Read Humorously Inappropriate Meanings Into Signs",
            "Answer": "Semiopathy",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Faint Trace Of Perfume Left In The Wake Of A Person Passing By",
            "Answer": "Sillage",
        },
        {
            "Question": "An Corner That’s Out Of The Way To Sit With Your Partner During A Dance, Also A Summerhouse",
            "Answer": "Sitooterie",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Something That Is Designed To Look Like It Does The Job It’s Supposed To Do",
            "Answer": "Skeuomorph",
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Loud, Obnoxious Speaker Or An Offensive Writer",
            "Answer": "Slangwhanger",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Soft Mud Or Ooze",
            "Answer": "Sleck",
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Priest Who Involves Himself In Extracurricular Activities With His Flock",
            "Answer": "Smellsmock",
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Term Used By Us Police To Describe The Sale Of Illegal Cigarettes",
            "Answer": "Smurfing",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Someone Who Pokes His Or Her Head Into A Pub To See If Anyone Might Buy Them A Drink",
            "Answer": "Snecklifter",
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Dishonest And Calculating Politician",
            "Answer": "Snollygoster",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Snow That’s Turned Into Mush",
            "Answer": "Snowbroth",
        },
        {
            "Question": "To Stride Around As If Very Busy When In Fact You’re Doing Nothing",
            "Answer": "Snudge",
        },
        {
            "Question": "To Move The Body In A Sprawling Manner",
            "Answer": "Spartle",
        },
        {
            "Question": "To Chase Girls Around The Haystacks After Dark",
            "Answer": "Sprunt",
        },
        {
            "Question": "To Crush With Criticism",
            "Answer": "Squabash",
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Half-Suppressed Laugh",
            "Answer": "Squirk",
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Bishop Who Is Also A Squire",
            "Answer": "Squishop",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Little Depression Left In Your Bed When You’ve Been Lying In It All Night",
            "Answer": "Staddle",
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Star Architect",
            "Answer": "Starchitect",
        },
        {
            "Question": "To Decorate Something With Stars",
            "Answer": "Starrify",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Spectacle Or Show",
            "Answer": "Steracle",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Act Of Sneezing",
            "Answer": "Sternutation",
        },
        {
            "Question": "To Perceive The Number Of Objects In A Group Without Actually Counting Them",
            "Answer": "Subitize",
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Rare Adjective Meaning Proud And Overbearing",
            "Answer": "Superbious",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Ringing Or Sound Of Bells",
            "Answer": "Tintinnabulation",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Dot Over An ‘I’ Or ‘J’",
            "Answer": "Tittle",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Cutting A Word In Two And Putting Another Word In The Middle",
            "Answer": "Tmesis",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Office Of An Interpreter",
            "Answer": "Truchmanry",
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Tall, Lanky, And Messy Person",
            "Answer": "Trypall",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Adjective Meaning Dizzy From Spinning Around",
            "Answer": "Turngiddy",
        },
        {
            "Question": "To Gossip Or Talk Idly",
            "Answer": "Twattle",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Overly Precious Or Nice",
            "Answer": "Twee",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Lying Awake Before Sunrise And Worrying",
            "Answer": "Uhtceare",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Someone Who Gives Opinions On Things Beyond Their Knowledge",
            "Answer": "Ultracrepidarian",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Flat Or Sour Wine",
            "Answer": "Vappa",
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Run Before A Leap",
            "Answer": "Vease",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Constant Or Obsessive Repetition Of Meaningless Words Or Phrases",
            "Answer": "Verbigeration",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Taking Of Honey From Beehives",
            "Answer": "Vindemy",
        },
        {
            "Question": "An Obslete Word Meaning ‘Neighborhood’",
            "Answer": "Voisinage",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Contrived, Affected, And Deliberate",
            "Answer": "Voulu",
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Scottish Word Meaning Exhausted Or Slightly Unwell",
            "Answer": "Wabbit",
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Scottish Word Meaning A Slight Touch Of Illness",
            "Answer": "Waff",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Unintelligible Sound Made By Many People Talking At Once",
            "Answer": "Walla Walla",
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Person Who Has A Wallet",
            "Answer": "Walleteer",
        },
        {
            "Question": "To Be Overcome With Indigestion",
            "Answer": "Wamblecropt",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Feigned Groaning",
            "Answer": "Whindling",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Counter-Clockwise Or Contrary",
            "Answer": "Widdershins",
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Gust Of Very Cold Wind Such As Found In Alaska",
            "Answer": "Williwaw",
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Woman’s Head Covering In Medieval Times",
            "Answer": "Wimple",
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Style Of Shoe Or Boot From The 1950S With A Long Pointed Toe",
            "Answer": "Winklepicker",
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Kind Of Very Tough And Sharp Steel Made In Southern India",
            "Answer": "Wootz",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Scottish Word Meaning To Wriggle Or Wallow",
            "Answer": "Worble",
        },
        {
            "Question": "To Gulp Something Down Quickly And Greedily",
            "Answer": "Xertz",
        },
        {
            "Question": "English Dialect Name For The Green Woodpecker",
            "Answer": "Yaffle",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Bad Luck That Occurs Just As Expected, The Opposite Of Serendipity",
            "Answer": "Zemblanity",
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Rhetorical Device Using Multiple Senses Of A Word At The Same Time",
            "Answer": "Zeugma",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Sound Made By Power Saws",
            "Answer": "Zinzulation",
        },
        {
            "Question": "An Outcry Of Joy, Especially By Several People At Once",
            "Answer": "Ziraleet",
        },
        {
            "Question": "A German Word That Explains The ‘Compulsion To Move’ When Playing Chess",
            "Answer": "Zugzwang",
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Drowsy And Silly State Of Body Or Mind",
            "Answer": "Zwodder",
        },
		{
            "Question": "A Pretentious Loiterer In A Religious House",
            "Answer": "Abbey-lubber",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Inability To Make Decisions",
            "Answer": "Abulia",
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Wart That Hangs Down Like A String",
            "Answer": "Acrochordon",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Plastic Tip On The End Of A Shoelace",
            "Answer": "Aglet",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Wire Cage Holding The Cork In A Bottle Of Champagne",
            "Answer": "Agraffe",
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Feverish Desire To Rip One’s Clothes Off",
            "Answer": "Apodysophilia",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Something That Appears Out Of Thin Air",
            "Answer": "Apport",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Copious But Meaningless Writing Or Talk",
            "Answer": "Argle-bargle",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Complete Freedom From Stress And Anxiety",
            "Answer": "Ataraxia",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Little Loops For A Belt On A Pair Of Trousers Or A Raincoat",
            "Answer": "Beckets",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Coarsly Abusive Language",
            "Answer": "Billingsgate",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Something That Wants To Be Grand But Is Only Bland",
            "Answer": "Blandiose",
        },
        {
            "Question": "To Brag Or Speak Pompously",
            "Answer": "Bloviate",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Delusion That You Are An Ox Or A Cow",
            "Answer": "Boanthropy",
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Strap That Holds Pant Legs In Place",
            "Answer": "Bowyang",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Hole In A Cask Or Barrel Where Liquid Is Poured In Or Drained Out",
            "Answer": "Bunghole",
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Shocking Thing",
            "Answer": "Bysen",
        },
        {
            "Question": "An Intense Flurry Of Activity To Finish Something By A Deadline",
            "Answer": "Charette",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Someone That Loves Nooks And Crannies",
            "Answer": "Chasmophile",
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Small Cheese",
            "Answer": "Cheeseling",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Another Name For Woodlice",
            "Answer": "Cheeselips",
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Rhetorical Device Of Repeating Some Words You’ve Used In Reverse Order",
            "Answer": "Chiasmus",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Noise That Feet Make When Your Shoes Are Full Of Water",
            "Answer": "Chork",
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Group Hired To Applaud At A Performance",
            "Answer": "Claque",
        },
        {
            "Question": "An Obsessive Desire To Lie Down",
            "Answer": "Clinomania",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Science Of Leg-Pulling",
            "Answer": "Codology",
        },
        {
            "Question": "To Feel Ill Because Of Excessive Eating Or Drinking",
            "Answer": "Crapulous",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Of Or Relating To Twilight",
            "Answer": "Crepuscular",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Bed Fluff That’s Lodged In Your Belly Button",
            "Answer": "Culf",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Shock You Feel When You First Jump Into Cold Water",
            "Answer": "Curglaff",
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Low Rumbling Sound Produced By The Bowels",
            "Answer": "Curmuring",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Loose Skin On A Cow’s Neck",
            "Answer": "Dewlap",
        },
        {
            "Question": "To Make Wet And Dirty By Dragging On The Ground",
            "Answer": "Draggle",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Decaying Matter In A Forest",
            "Answer": "Duff",
        },
        {
            "Question": "To Lay A Bottle On Its Side Long Enough To Drain The Few Drops Remaining",
            "Answer": "Duffifie",
        },
        {
            "Question": "German Word For The False Sensation Of Movement Felt When Looking Out Of A Stopped Train, You See Another Train Depart",
            "Answer": "Eisenbahnscheinbewegung",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Final Individual In A Species",
            "Answer": "Endling",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Constantly Hungry",
            "Answer": "Famelicose",
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Dangling Piece Of Curly Hair",
            "Answer": "Feat",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Metal Part Of A Pencil",
            "Answer": "Ferrule",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Having The Color Of A Dead Or Faded Leaf",
            "Answer": "Feuillemorte",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Someone Who Is Very Free With Money, Is A Generous Spender",
            "Answer": "Flahoolick",
        },
        {
            "Question": "To Laugh In A Disrespectful Or Jeering Way",
            "Answer": "Fleer",
        },
        {
            "Question": "To Behave In A Cowardly Manner",
            "Answer": "Flink",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Feverishly Plucking At The Bed Linens",
            "Answer": "Flocculating",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Sucking Honey From Flowers",
            "Answer": "Florisugent",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Overwhelmed By Unreasonable And Disproportionate Scolding",
            "Answer": "Forflitten",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Weary With Being Tossed About",
            "Answer": "Forwallowed",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Pretending To Work",
            "Answer": "Fudgelling",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Tightrope Walking",
            "Answer": "Funambuling",
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Legal Term Describing Goods Or Money That Can Be Replaced By Equivalent Items",
            "Answer": "Fungible",
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Wandering Beggar",
            "Answer": "Gaberlunzie",
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Warning Cry Shouted Before Throwing Slops From An Upstairs Window",
            "Answer": "Gardyloo",
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Gaelic Word For Both A Beautiful Fairy And A Hag In The Shape Of A Goat.",
            "Answer": "Glaistig",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Substance That Collects In The Bottom Of Your Pockets",
            "Answer": "Gnurr",
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Person Who Believes Everything He Or She Hears",
            "Answer": "Gobemouche",
        },
        {
            "Question": "One Who Stares For A Long Time At Things Happening On A Canal",
            "Answer": "Gongoozler",
        },
        {
            "Question": "To Have A Paralyzing Or Mesmerizing Effect On Someone",
            "Answer": "Gorgonize",
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Surgical Sponge Accidentally Left Inside A Patient’s Body",
            "Answer": "Gossypiboma",
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Double Handful Of Water",
            "Answer": "Gowpen",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Word For A High-Spirited Person In The 14Th Century",
            "Answer": "Great-willy",
        },
        {
            "Question": "To Silently Watch People While They’re Eating, Hoping They’ll Ask You To Join Them",
            "Answer": "Groak",
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Musical Timing Of 1/64",
            "Answer": "Hemidemisemiquaver",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Fear Of Long Words",
            "Answer": "Hippopotomonstrosesquippedaliophobia",
        },
        {
            "Question": "To Disgust Even Yourself",
            "Answer": "Idiorepulsive",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Excessive Reference To Oneself In The Third Person",
            "Answer": "Illeism",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Australian Word Meaning ‘A Small-Time Confidence Trickster’",
            "Answer": "Illywhacker",
        },
        {
            "Question": "This Word Is Used To Yell At Your Suboordinates When They’re Not Being Productive Enough",
            "Answer": "Imshi",
        },
        {
            "Question": "To Hide In The Bathroom",
            "Answer": "Incloacate",
        },
        {
            "Question": "To Apply Ointment To Someone Or Something",
            "Answer": "Inunct",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Breakfasty, Breakfastish, Of Or Relating To Breakfast",
            "Answer": "Jentacular",
        },
        {
            "Question": "To Fidget Or Shuffle",
            "Answer": "Jiffle",
        },
        {
            "Question": "To Pour With An Unsteady Hand",
            "Answer": "Jirble",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Death Caused By Overwork Or Job-Related Exhaustion",
            "Answer": "Karoshi",
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Scottish Word Meaning ‘Consipicuous, Easily Recognizable’",
            "Answer": "Kenspeckle",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Graffiti Found In Restrooms",
            "Answer": "Latrinalia",
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Fawning Person Who Is Eager To Obey Those In Power",
            "Answer": "Lickspittle",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Tail Of A Graduate’s Hood",
            "Answer": "Liripoop",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The White, Crescent Shaped Part At The Base Of A Nail",
            "Answer": "Lunule",
        },
        {
            "Question": "An Old Hag",
            "Answer": "Mackabroin",
        },
        {
            "Question": "To Blur In Printing",
            "Answer": "Mackle",
        },
        {
            "Question": "To Treat Someone Very Indulgently Or Protectively",
            "Answer": "Mollycoddle",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Strip Of Wood Or Metal That Separates Panes Of Glass In A Window",
            "Answer": "Muntin",
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Word Meaning Muttering, Murmuring.",
            "Answer": "Mussitation",
        },
        {
            "Question": "An Adjective That Means ‘More Than Usually Susceptible To The Cold’",
            "Answer": "Nesh",
        },
        {
            "Question": "To Build A Nest",
            "Answer": "Nidify",
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Person Who Deals With Things Of No Importance",
            "Answer": "Nihilarian",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Pleasurable Anticipation Of Success Before Any Actual Work Has Been Done",
            "Answer": "Nikhedonia",
        },
        {
            "Question": "An Effeminate Fellow, Especially Well-Dressed And Popular With Women",
            "Answer": "Nimfadoro",
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Lover Of Wine",
            "Answer": "Oenophile",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Fear Of Belly Buttons",
            "Answer": "Omphalophobia",
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Person Who Illegally Exports Sheep",
            "Answer": "Owler",
        },
        {
            "Question": "An Old Document In Which The Original Writing Has Been Scraped Off So That New Words Can Be Written Over It",
            "Answer": "Palimpsest",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Characterized By Extreme Optimism, Especially In The Face Of Adversity",
            "Answer": "Panglossian",
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Tax On Keeping Pigs In Royal Forests That Was Paid In Pigs",
            "Answer": "Pannage",
        },
        {
            "Question": "To Hold A Meeting While Walking",
            "Answer": "Pedeconference",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Other Side To A Hammer’s Striking Side",
            "Answer": "Peen",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Pleasant Smell That Accompanies Rain",
            "Answer": "Petrichor",
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Lawyer Whose Methods Are Underhanded Or Disreputable",
            "Answer": "Pettifogger",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Lights You See If You Close Your Eyes And Press Your Hands To Them",
            "Answer": "Phosphenes",
        },
        {
            "Question": "What You Call The Spots On Dice And Dominoes",
            "Answer": "Pips",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Offspring Of A Polar Bear And A Grizzly Bear",
            "Answer": "Pizzly Bear",
        },
        {
            "Question": "An Adjective Meaning ‘Liking To Wander’",
            "Answer": "Planeticose",
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Person Who Finds Joy And Comfort In Rainy Days",
            "Answer": "Pluviophile",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Fear Of Beards",
            "Answer": "Pogonophobia",
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Person Whose Job It Is To Taste Meats And Drinks Before Serving Them",
            "Answer": "Pregustator",
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Rare Word Meaning ‘Made With Gruel’",
            "Answer": "Pulmentarious",
        },
        {
            "Question": "An Adjective Meaning ‘Like Birds That Roll Themselves In Dust’ Or ‘Dust-Colored’",
            "Answer": "Pulveratricious",
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Stocky Person With A Rounded Body And Head, Thick Trunk, And A Tendency To Fat",
            "Answer": "Pyknic",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Season For Drinking",
            "Answer": "Quafftide",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Resembling A Marsh, Soggy And Soft",
            "Answer": "Quaggy",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The First Person You Meet After Leaving Your House On Some Special Occasion",
            "Answer": "Qualtagh",
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Small Shoot That Grows From The Root Of A Plant",
            "Answer": "Ratoon",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Foggy, Damp, And Cold",
            "Answer": "Rawky",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Seemingly Malevolent Bahavior Of Inanimate Objects",
            "Answer": "Resistentialism",
        },
        {
            "Question": "An Adjective Meaning Behind The Times Or Characteristic Of An Earlier Period",
            "Answer": "Retardataire",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Hairless And Moist Nose Of Some Animals",
            "Answer": "Rhinarium",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Medical Condition Otherwise Known As ‘A Runny Nose’",
            "Answer": "Rhinorrhea",
        },
        {
            "Question": "High-Waisted Skiing Pants With Shoulder Straps",
            "Answer": "Salopettes",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Unstressed, Flat Vowel Sound That Isn’t Represented By Any Of The Available Vowels",
            "Answer": "Schwa",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Collection Of Stock And Bond Certificates As Works Of Art",
            "Answer": "Scripophily",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Unfair Description Of Something Said Or Done To Make People Have A Bad Opinion Of Someone",
            "Answer": "Scurrilous",
        },
        {
            "Question": "An Adjective Meaning Unfamiliar, Rare, Strange, And Wonderful",
            "Answer": "Selcouth",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Tendency To Read Humorously Inappropriate Meanings Into Signs",
            "Answer": "Semiopathy",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Faint Trace Of Perfume Left In The Wake Of A Person Passing By",
            "Answer": "Sillage",
        },
        {
            "Question": "An Corner That’s Out Of The Way To Sit With Your Partner During A Dance, Also A Summerhouse",
            "Answer": "Sitooterie",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Something That Is Designed To Look Like It Does The Job It’s Supposed To Do",
            "Answer": "Skeuomorph",
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Loud, Obnoxious Speaker Or An Offensive Writer",
            "Answer": "Slangwhanger",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Soft Mud Or Ooze",
            "Answer": "Sleck",
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Priest Who Involves Himself In Extracurricular Activities With His Flock",
            "Answer": "Smellsmock",
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Term Used By Us Police To Describe The Sale Of Illegal Cigarettes",
            "Answer": "Smurfing",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Someone Who Pokes His Or Her Head Into A Pub To See If Anyone Might Buy Them A Drink",
            "Answer": "Snecklifter",
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Dishonest And Calculating Politician",
            "Answer": "Snollygoster",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Snow That’s Turned Into Mush",
            "Answer": "Snowbroth",
        },
        {
            "Question": "To Stride Around As If Very Busy When In Fact You’re Doing Nothing",
            "Answer": "Snudge",
        },
        {
            "Question": "To Move The Body In A Sprawling Manner",
            "Answer": "Spartle",
        },
        {
            "Question": "To Chase Girls Around The Haystacks After Dark",
            "Answer": "Sprunt",
        },
        {
            "Question": "To Crush With Criticism",
            "Answer": "Squabash",
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Half-Suppressed Laugh",
            "Answer": "Squirk",
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Bishop Who Is Also A Squire",
            "Answer": "Squishop",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Little Depression Left In Your Bed When You’ve Been Lying In It All Night",
            "Answer": "Staddle",
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Star Architect",
            "Answer": "Starchitect",
        },
        {
            "Question": "To Decorate Something With Stars",
            "Answer": "Starrify",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Spectacle Or Show",
            "Answer": "Steracle",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Act Of Sneezing",
            "Answer": "Sternutation",
        },
        {
            "Question": "To Perceive The Number Of Objects In A Group Without Actually Counting Them",
            "Answer": "Subitize",
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Rare Adjective Meaning Proud And Overbearing",
            "Answer": "Superbious",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Ringing Or Sound Of Bells",
            "Answer": "Tintinnabulation",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Dot Over An ‘I’ Or ‘J’",
            "Answer": "Tittle",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Cutting A Word In Two And Putting Another Word In The Middle",
            "Answer": "Tmesis",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Office Of An Interpreter",
            "Answer": "Truchmanry",
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Tall, Lanky, And Messy Person",
            "Answer": "Trypall",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Adjective Meaning Dizzy From Spinning Around",
            "Answer": "Turngiddy",
        },
        {
            "Question": "To Gossip Or Talk Idly",
            "Answer": "Twattle",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Overly Precious Or Nice",
            "Answer": "Twee",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Lying Awake Before Sunrise And Worrying",
            "Answer": "Uhtceare",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Someone Who Gives Opinions On Things Beyond Their Knowledge",
            "Answer": "Ultracrepidarian",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Flat Or Sour Wine",
            "Answer": "Vappa",
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Run Before A Leap",
            "Answer": "Vease",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Constant Or Obsessive Repetition Of Meaningless Words Or Phrases",
            "Answer": "Verbigeration",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Taking Of Honey From Beehives",
            "Answer": "Vindemy",
        },
        {
            "Question": "An Obslete Word Meaning ‘Neighborhood’",
            "Answer": "Voisinage",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Contrived, Affected, And Deliberate",
            "Answer": "Voulu",
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Scottish Word Meaning Exhausted Or Slightly Unwell",
            "Answer": "Wabbit",
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Scottish Word Meaning A Slight Touch Of Illness",
            "Answer": "Waff",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Unintelligible Sound Made By Many People Talking At Once",
            "Answer": "Walla Walla",
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Person Who Has A Wallet",
            "Answer": "Walleteer",
        },
        {
            "Question": "To Be Overcome With Indigestion",
            "Answer": "Wamblecropt",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Feigned Groaning",
            "Answer": "Whindling",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Counter-Clockwise Or Contrary",
            "Answer": "Widdershins",
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Gust Of Very Cold Wind Such As Found In Alaska",
            "Answer": "Williwaw",
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Woman’s Head Covering In Medieval Times",
            "Answer": "Wimple",
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Style Of Shoe Or Boot From The 1950S With A Long Pointed Toe",
            "Answer": "Winklepicker",
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Kind Of Very Tough And Sharp Steel Made In Southern India",
            "Answer": "Wootz",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Scottish Word Meaning To Wriggle Or Wallow",
            "Answer": "Worble",
        },
        {
            "Question": "To Gulp Something Down Quickly And Greedily",
            "Answer": "Xertz",
        },
        {
            "Question": "English Dialect Name For The Green Woodpecker",
            "Answer": "Yaffle",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Bad Luck That Occurs Just As Expected, The Opposite Of Serendipity",
            "Answer": "Zemblanity",
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Rhetorical Device Using Multiple Senses Of A Word At The Same Time",
            "Answer": "Zeugma",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Sound Made By Power Saws",
            "Answer": "Zinzulation",
        },
        {
            "Question": "An Outcry Of Joy, Especially By Several People At Once",
            "Answer": "Ziraleet",
        },
        {
            "Question": "A German Word That Explains The ‘Compulsion To Move’ When Playing Chess",
            "Answer": "Zugzwang",
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Drowsy And Silly State Of Body Or Mind",
            "Answer": "Zwodder",
        }
    ]
}